optimalfusion.com 2017-12-19

# Optimal Fusion Privacy Policy | Performance Driven Integrated Media

**Privacy Policy – Your Privacy Rights**

_Effective Date: May 10, 2012_

**What information does OptimalFusion™ collect and how does OptimalFusion™ use it?**

This Privacy Policy describes the information practices of the OptimalFusion™ website, operated by Optimal Fusion. You may visit and use certain features of our website without any registration, in which case none of your personal information will be collected or retained. However, if you to register through our website or request coupons, we will ask you to provide personal information such as your contact information and your date of birth.

In addition, some sections of our website allow you to provide information directly to third parties whose websites are framed within our website, as described below in the section on “Third party links and co-brand relationships.”

We may collect data for our own use from your computer or device when you are visiting an OptimalFusion™ web site or on a third party’s behalf when we serve advertisements on our network of web sites. We may also collect data on third-party web sites for our own use. This data may include information such as your IP address, web pages which have been viewed by you, date and time, domain type, and your responses to an advertisement delivered by us or a third party advertising technology vendor. This is information which does not immediately reveal your identity. Nor will we use this information to attempt to discern your identity

We may use different types of technologies, such as cookies, pixels, and other technologies to collect this data. We do not collect the following information that identifies you: your name, address, email address, and telephone number (“Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”) unless you choose to provide it to us. We do not combine the data we collect with this PII.

We do not ask for PII other than as outlined below for business purposes. We don’t collect PII via our corporate web site, www.optimalfusion.com unless you choose to provide it to us – for example, by sending us your PII in an email. Some of our partner websites may ask people to register and provide PII. None of this PII is combined by Optimal Fusion with other data and/or used by Optimal Fusion for our ad serving.

We use the information we collect to provide you with product promotions, support and any information you request, and otherwise to operate our business and this website.

**How does OptimalFusion™ protect visitor information?**

OptimalFusion™ uses reasonable security measures to help protect the information that we collect.

**Does OptimalFusion™ use “cookies”?**

We use cookies so that we can help provide our customers with a better and more efficient experience on our website. A “cookie” is a piece of information a web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the web site to remember who you are without personally identifying you. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access all of the features on our website.

**Does OptimalFusion™ disclose any information it collects from its visitors to third parties?**

OptimalFusion™ may share the information you provide to us with third parties to allow these third parties to contact you and provide you offers and other information that they think will be valuable to you. OptimalFusion™ does not control the policies or practices of other entities with which we may share data. If you would like to learn about the policies and practices of these third parties or any choices they may offer, you should contact them directly.

OptimalFusion™ may share your information with our affiliates or with service providers and vendors who work on our behalf, and these third parties may further disclose the information they receive from us. OptimalFusion™ may use, sell or transfer any anonymous or aggregated statistical user data in any manner at any time. We may also disclose your personal information to protect the Company or our legal rights or when required to do so by law, including in response to a search warrant, subpoena, court order, or request from a law enforcement agency. We may transfer information to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

**What are my choices?**

If you would like OptimalFusion™ to stop providing your information to these third parties, please send a “do not share” request to OptimalFusion™ by emailing us at [privacy@optimalfusion.com](mailto:privacy@optimalfusion.com), or by contacting us as directed below under “Additional Information.”

Here are some additional resources that can help you manage your experiences with the various advertisers that you may come in contact with on Optimal Fusion’s websites:

Opt-out mechanism(s) at the Network Advertising Initiative : [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)  
Self regulatory Program for Behavioral Advertising Consumer Choice Page opt out page : <http://www.aboutads.info/>

**OptimalFusion™’s special note to parents**

OptimalFusion™ does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Third party websites, data collection, links and co-brand relationships**

In order to provide increased value to our visitors, OptimalFusion™ may choose various third party websites to link to and from, and frame within, its own website. OptimalFusion™ may also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer information, programs and other services and features to its users. A “framed” website is a page from a third party’s website that appears within our website. Framing allows you to interact with a third party website without navigating away from our website.

These third party web sites may independently solicit and collect information from you. OptimalFusion™ does not control these linked sites. Since their treatment of personal information may differ from ours, we encourage you to carefully review the privacy statements and terms of use of all third party web sites you access. On occasion, those third party web sites may provide us with information about your use of those sites.

**Your consent and changes to this policy**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by OptimalFusion™ as set forth in this Privacy Statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. Continued access or use of the website shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this Privacy Statement.

**Additional information**

This notice details the privacy policies of OptimalFusion™ for all of its users of its website with regard to information collected through this website. If you have questions regarding this policy or the practices of OptimalFusion™, contact us at OptimalFusion™, Privacy Division, located at 7162 Beverly Blvd, #580, Los Angeles, CA 90036.
